dreshare.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy

**Personal Identification Information**

**www.dreshare.com** will collect some Personal Identification Information (PII) like Name, email, address of a website user on several occasion. However, users are always free to refuse any submission of these PII while using this site.

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

While using this site ( **www.dreshare.com** ) we may also collect some Non-personal Identification Information (NPII) like Browser name, IP address, ISP name and other related information of the user.

**Web Browser Cookies & Log Files**

Like all another website, **www.dreshare.com** also uses specific technology like “ **Cookies & log files**” to gather data on the usage of our website. Web browser places a cookie on the hard disk of the user to log information about them. Site users are always free to customize their web browser to refuse cookies or set an alert about cookies. However, if they block cookies, then maybe some part of the website will be not accessible properly.

**GDPR Policy**

**www.dreshare.com** has a concern to protect the data of the user. Therefore, we are practicing all the guidelines which are told by the **EU General Data Protection Regulation** (GDPR). www.dreshare.com **will not sell** or **give** any type of **user’s data** to the third party.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Our website is not meant to collect or maintain information of a person under 13 year age mark. In addition to this, no part of this website ( **www.dreshare.com** ) is designed to attract child under 13 years old.

**Usage of Collected Information?**

  * We always try to use collected data to improve our website according to the user feedback data and other information.
  * Collected information will be used to support and respond site user properly.

**Protection of User Information?**

We have adopted a proper practice to collect, use and protect site user’s data. Many sensitive information exchanges between **www.dreshare.com** and user are held on SSL secure platform channel. This SSL medium is well encrypted and protected with a digital signature.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

**www.dreshare.com** will hold the right to change this privacy policy at any time without notifying anyone. However, for this reason, we always suggest our site user to regularly visit this privacy policy page for an update.

**Your Acceptance Of These Terms**

You can use our website if you are agreed to this privacy policy and term of use. However, if you do not agree to these terms you are not allowed to use our site. Therefore, your acceptance of these terms is required to use this site.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any question to this privacy policy then feel free to contact us at this email address: **[contact@dreshare.com](mailto:contact@dreshare.com) **
